Guide to the Donald Oliver/Chelsea Music Archive, 1907-2008 (bulk 1962-1991) MSS.254
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Librettos and Playbills
  - Flowers for Algernon, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Book and Lyrics by David Rodgers Music by Charles Strouse
  - Flying Colors: A Revue, [1932] (Box 6, Folder 9)
    By Howard Dietz Music and lyrics by Howard Dietz and Arthur Schwartz
  - Flying High: A Musical Comedy in Two Acts and Thirteen Scenes, [1930] (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Book by [B. G.] DeSylva, Brown, Henderson and Jack McGowan
  - Follies, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Book by James Goldman Music and Lyrics by Stephen Sondheim
  - Follies, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Follow Thru!, January 9, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Book by Laurence Schwab and B. G. De Sylva Music by Ray Henderson Lyrics by Lew Brown and B. G. De Sylva
  - Footsteps: A Thriller, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    By Ira Levin
  - Footsteps: A Thriller, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    by Ira Levin
  - Forty-Five Minutes from Broadway, undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Book by George M. Cohan
  - Forty-Second Street, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Book by Michael Stewart and Mark Bramble Music by Harry Warren Lyrics by Al Dubin
  - Foxy: A New Musical, [1964] (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Book by Ian McLellan Hunter and Ring Lardner, Jr. Music by Robert Emmett Dolan Lyrics by Johnny Mercer
  - Frank's Wild Years, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Book by Kathleen Brennan and Tom Waits Music and Lyrics by Tom Waits
  - Gantry: A Musical [revised], [1970] (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Book by Terry Miller Music by Stanley Lebowsky Lyrics by Fred Tobias
  - The Garfield Nude: A New Musical Comedy, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Book by George Linsenmann and Ralph Falco Music by George Linsenmann Lyrics by Ralph Falco
  - The Garrick Gaieties, [1926] (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Garrick Gaieties, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Gay Divorce, [1932] (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Book by Dwight Tayler Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter
  - The Gay Life, August 28, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Book by Fay and Michael Kanin Music by Arthur Schwartz Lyrics by Howard Dietz
    Rehearsal script Contains annotations
  - The Gay Life, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Gentlemen, Be Seated!, undated (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Gentlemen Prefer Blondes, [1949] (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Book by Joseph Fields and Anita Loos Music by Jule Styne Lyrics by Leo Robin
  - Gentlemen Unafraid, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Book and Lyrics by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein Music by Jerome Kern
  - George M!, [1968] (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Book by Michael Stewart Music and Lyrics by George M. Cohan
  - George White's Scandals, 8th Edition "1926" (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - George White's Scandals, 9th Edition, 1928 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - George White's Scandals, 10th Edition, [1929] (Box 7, Folder 5)
    by George White and William K. Wells
  - George White's Scandals, 11th Edition, 1931 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - George White's Scandals, November 1933 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Second script
  - George White's Scandals, 1936 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - George White's Scandals of 1936 - stage version: A Musical Revue in Two Acts (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Book by George White [Music by Ray Henderson]
  - Georgy!: A Musical [rehearsal script], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Book by Tom Mankiewicz Music by George Fischoff Lyrics by Carole Bayer
  - The Ghost and Mrs. Muir [first draft], February 26, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Book by Arthur Marx and Robert Fisher
  - The Ghost and Mrs. Muir Supplemental Material, [1995] (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Gigi, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Book and Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner Music by Frederick Loewe
  - Girl Crazy: A Musical Comedy in Two Acts, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Book by Guy Bolton and Jack McGowan Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - The Girl Friend: A Musical Comedy, [1926] (Box 7, Folder 15)
    By Herbert Fields Lyrics by Lorenz Hart Music by Richard Rogers
  - The Girl in Pink Tights, [1954] (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Book by Jerome Chodorov and Joseph Fields Music by Sigmund Romberg Lyrics by Leo Robin
  - The Girl Who Came To Supper, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - The Girls Upstairs, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - The Girls Upstairs [revised draft], 1968 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Book by James Goldman Music and Lyrics by Stephem Sondheim
  - Going Hollywood: A Musical Version of Hart and Kaufman's "Once in a Lifetime" [revised edition], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Book by Joseph Leonardo and David Zippel Music by Jonathan Sheffer Lyrics by Davd Zippel
  - Going Up, undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Book by Otto Harbach Music by Lou Hirsch
  - Going Up, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Book by Otto Harbach Music by Lou Hirsch Based on James Montcomery's play "The Aviator"
  - Gone with the Wind: The Epic Musical [second draft], 1971 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Adaptation by Horton Foote Music and Lyrics by Harold Rome
  - Good, Good Friends: A New Musical Comedy, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Book by Patrick Dennis Music and Lyrics by Murray Grand
  - The Goodbye Girl: A New Musical [4th draft], June 1992 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Book by Neil Simon Music by Marvin Hamlisch Lyrics by David Zippel
  - Goodbye, Mr. Chips: A New Musical, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Book by Roland Starke Music and Lyrics by Leslie Bricusse
  - Got Tu Go Disco, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Book by John Zodrow
  - [The Graduate, Based on] [revised], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Bob Merrill
  - Grand Hotel: The Musical [final script], November 12 1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Book by Luther Davis Music by Robert Wright and George Forrest Lyrics by Robert Wright
  - Great Expectations: A Musical Play, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Book by Drew Kalter Music and Lyrics by Jeremiah Murray
  - Great Lady [personal copy, Dwight Deere Wiman], 1938 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Book by Earle Crooker and Lowell Brentano Music by Frederick Loewe Lyrics by Earle Crooker
  - The Great Waltz, undated (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Greenwillow, [1960] (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Book by Lesser Samuels and Frank Loesser Music and Lyrics by Frank Loesser
  - Grind: A New Musical, [1985] (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Booy by Fay Kanin Music by Larry Grossman Lyrics by Ellen Fitzhugh
  - Grind: A New Musical [rehearsal script], [1985] (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Book by Fay Kanin Music by Larry Grossman Lyrics by Ellen Fitzhugh
  - H.R.H.: Wallis and David in Nassau [revised], January 1995 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    by Snoo Wilson
  - Hair: The American Tribal-Love Rock Musical, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Book and Lyrics by Gerome Ragni and James Rado Music by Galt MacDermot
  - Hallelujah, Baby! [corrected copy], 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Book by Arthur Laurents Music by Jule Styne Lyrics by Betty Comden and Adolph Green
  - Hannah…1939, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    by Bob Merrill
  - The Happiest Girl in the World, [1961] (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Book by Fred Saidy and Henry Myers Music by Jacques Offenbach Lyrics by E.Y Harburg
  - Happy New Year, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Book by Philip Barry songs by Cole Porter
  - Harrigan & Hart [rehearsal draft], 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Book by Michael Stewart Music by MAx Showalter Lyrics by Peter Walker
  - Having a Ball, January 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    By Alan Bleasdale Re-written version
  - Hazel Flagg, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Book by Ben Hecht Music by Jule Styne Lyrics by Bob Hilliard
  - Heads Up, [1929] (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Book by John McGowan and Paul Gerard Smith Music by Richard Rodgers and Lorenz Hart
  - Helen of Troy, N.Y. [playing version], July 10, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Book by Geroge Kaufman and Marc Connelly Music by Harry Ruby Lyrics by Bert Kalmar
  - Hellzapoppin! [rehearsal script], October 18, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    by Abe Burrows, Bill Heyer and Hank Beebe
  - Help! Help! Hooray!, December 10, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    by Betty Comden and Adolph Green
  - Her First Roman: A Musical, [1968] (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Book, Music and Lyrics by Ervin Drake
  - Here's Love!, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Book, Music and Lyrics by Meredith Willson
  - The Hero, Sherman Frank copy [corrected copy], [1960] (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Book by Larry Gelbart Lyrics by Norman Gimbal Music by Moose Charlop
  - Hi, Rudy: A Musical Comedy, undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Book by Garinei and Giovannini
  - High Button Shoes, [1947] (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Book by Stephen Longstreet Music by Jule Styne Lyrics by Sammy Cahn
  - High Spirits: A New Musical [playing version], April 7, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Book, Music and Lyrics by Hugh Martin and Timothy Gray
  - Higher and Higher, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Book by Gladys Hurlbut and Joshua Logan Music by Richard Rodgers Lyrics by Lorenz Hart
  - Hit the Deck [original], [1927] (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Hit the Deck: A Nautical Musical Comedy [revised version], [1927] (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Book by Herbert Fields Music by Vincent Youmans Lyrics by Leo Robbins and Clifford Grey
  - Hoagy and Bix: A New Musical, undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Book by William L. Wheatley
  - Hold Everything, October 10, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Book by B.G. DeSylva Music by Ray Henderson Lyrics by B.G. DeSylva and Lew Brown
  - The Hollywood Pinafore, or The Lad who Loved a Salary, [1945] (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Book and Lyrics by George S. Kaufman Music by Sir Arthur Sullivan
  - Holly Golightly playbill, Shubert Theatre, October 31, 1966; November 7, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Book by Abe Burrows Music and Lyrics by Bob Merrill
  - Hooray for What, [1937] (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Book by Howard Lindsay and Russel Crouse Music by Harold Arlen Lyrics by E.Y. Harburg
  - Hot-Cha!, March 8, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Book by Lew Brown, Ray Henderson, Mark Hellinger and Hy Kraft Music by Ray Henderson Lyrics by Lew Brown
  - Hot September, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Book by Paul Osborn Music by Kenneth Jacobson Lyrics by Rhoda Roberts
  - Hot Spot, January 3, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Book by Jack Weinstock and Willie Gilbert Music by Mary Rodgers Lyrics by Martin Charnin
  - House of Flowers: A Musical Play, [1954] (Box 9, Folder 8)
    by Truman Capote and Harold Arlen
  - House of Flowers: A Musical Play, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Book by Truman Capote Music by Harold Arlen Lyrics by Truman Capote and Harold Arlen
  - How Do You Do I Love You, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Book by Michael Stewart Music by David Shire Lyrics by Richard Maltby
  - Hubba Hubba, 1970 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - The Hunchback of Notre Dame [final stage version], 1998 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - I, Anastasia: A Musical Play, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Book by Guy Bolton Music and Lyrics by Robert Wright and George Forrest
  - I and Albert, June 1985 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Book by Jay Allen Music by Charles Strouse Lyrics by Lee Adams
  - I Do, I Do: A Musical About Marriage, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - I Had a Ball: A New Musical, August 1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Book by Jerome Chodorov Music and Lyrics by Jack Lawrence and Stan Freeman
  - I Love My Wife, [1977] (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Book and Lyrics by Michael Stewart Music by Cy Coleman
  - I Married a Witch, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Book and Lyrics by Laurence Holzman and Felicia Needleman
  - I Married an Angel: A Musical Comedy, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - I Married an Angel, [1938] (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - I Remember Mama: The New Musical [rehearsal script], January 23, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Book by Thomas Meehan Music by Richard Rodgers Lyrics by Martin Charnin
  - If I were Queen, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Book by [Polan] Banks and Wi[...]ia[m] Caxton Music by J. [Pr...] [...] Lyrics by Ogden [...]
  - If the Shoe Fits, [1946] (Box 9, Folder 22)
    Book by June Carroll and Robert Duke Music by David Raskin Lyrics by June Carroll
  - Illya Darling, [1967] (Box 9, Folder 23)
    Book by Jules Dassin Music by Manos Hadjidakis Lyrics by Joe Darion
  - In Person: A Musical Play [rehearsal draft], May 31, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    Book by George Furth Music by John Kander Lyrics by Fred Ebb
  - Inner City: A Street Cantata, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    Music by Helen Miller Lyrics by Eve Merriam
  - Into the Woods [incomplete draft], May 27, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    Music and lyrics by Stephen Sondheim Book by James Lapine
    Incomplete first draft
  - Into the Woods, December 22, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Irene: A Musical Comedy, [1919] (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Book by James Montgomery Music by Harry Tierney Lyrics by Joseph McCarthy
  - Irene, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Book by Hugh Wheeler and Joseph Stein Music by Harry Tierney Lyrics by Joseph McCarthy
  - Irma-La-Douche: A Musical Comedy, [1960] (Box 10, Folder 3)
    English Book and Lyrics by Julian More, David Heneker and Monty Norman Music by Marguerite Monnot
  - Newspaper clipping: "It's just Vaudeville, but it has a plot, too", undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - It's a Bird… It's a Plane… It's SUPERMAN: The New Musical Comedy [final playing version], March 29, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Book by David Newman and Robert Benton Music by Charles Strouse Lyrics by Lee Adams
  - It's Superman!: The Super Musical [revised], October 1, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Jackpot, [1944] (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Book by Guy Bolton, Sidney Sheldon and Ben Roberts Music by Vernon Duke Lyrics by Howard Dietz
  - Jamaica, [1957] (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Book by E.Y. Harburg and Fred Saidy Music by Harold Arlen Lyrics by E.Y. Harburg
  - The Jazz Singer: A New Musical [workshop rehearsal draft], 1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Book by Sherman Yellen Music and Lyrics by Will Holt
  - Jelly's Last Jam [workshop rehearsal script], 1991 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Jelly's Last Jam, June 17, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Jennie [second draft], [1963] (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Book by Arnold Schulman Music and Lyrics by Howard Dietz and Arthur Schwartz
  - Jennie, [1963] (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Jesus Christ Superstar, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Music by Andrew Lloyd Webber Lyrics by Tim Rice
  - Jubilee!, [1935] (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Book by Moss Hart Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter
  - Jumbo, [1935] (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Book by Ben Hecht and Charles Macarthur Music by Richard Rodgers Lyrics by Lorenz Hart
  - June Moon: A Comedy, 1930 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    By Ring Lardner and George S. Kaufman
  - Juno [final revised script], [1959] (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Book by Joseph Stein Music and Lyrics by Marc Blitzstein
  - Kean, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Book by Peter Stone Music and Lyrics by Robert Wright and George Forrest
  - Kelly: A Musical in Two Acts [revised script], 1964 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Book and Lyrics by Eddie Lawrence Music by Moose Charlap
  - Kelly: A Musical in Two Acts, [1965] (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Kicks: The Showgirl Musical [workshop IV], June 25, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Book and Lyrics by Tom Eyen Music by Alan Menken
  - Kings and Cabbages: A New Musical, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Book by Hugh Wheeler Music by Vernon Duke Lyrics by Martin Charnin
  - Kiss of the Spiderwoman, July 1989 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    Book by Terrence McNally Music by John Kander Lyrics by Fred Ebb
  - Kiss of the Spider Woman, February 1990 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Book by Terrence McNally (based on the novel by Manuel Puig) Music by John Kander Lyrics by Fred Ebb Directed by Harold Prince
    Rehearsal version contains marginalia
  - The Knife [corrected copy, version D], January 5, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Book by David Hare Music by Nick Bicat Lyrics by Tim Rose Price
  - Kwamina, [1961] (Box 10, Folder 27)
    Book by Robert Alan Aurthur Music and Lyrics by Richard Adler
  - Ladies In Waiting, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  - Lady Be Good, [1924] (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Book by Guy Bolton and Fred Thompson Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - Lady in the Dark, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Book by Moss Hart Music by Kurt Weill Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - The Last Minstrel Show, 1979 (Box 72, Folder 18)
  - Late Nite Comic, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Book by Allan Knee Music and Lyrics by Brian Gari
  - Leave it to Jane: Musical Comedy in Two Acts, [1917] (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Book and Lyrics by Guy Bolton and P.G. Wodehouse Music by Jerome Kern
  - Legs Diamond [revised book], November 12, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Book by Irvin S. Bauer and Charles Suppon Music and Lyrics by Peter Allen
  - Leonard Sillman's New Faces of 1936 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Leonard Sillman's New Faces of 1952 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Leonard Stillman's New Faces of '56, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Music and Lyrics by Ronny Graham
  - Let it Ride, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Let's Face It, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Book by Dorothy and Herbert Fields Songs by Cole Porter
  - Life Begins at 8:40, [1934] (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Life Begins at 8:40, [1934] (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Li'l Abner: An Original Musical Comedy, [1956] (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Book by Norman Panama and Melvin Frank Music and Lyrics by Johnny Mercer and Gene de Paul
  - The Lion King [stage adaptation], August 5, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Book by Roger Allers and Irene Mecchi Music by Elton John Lyrics by Tim Rice
  - Little Johnny Jones, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Boob by George M. Cohan
  - Little Me [3rd draft], 1981 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Book by Neil Simon Music by Cy Coleman Lyrics by Carolyn Leigh
  - Little Nelly Kelly, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
    by George M. Cohan
  - The Little Show, undated (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Lolita, My Love: A Musical Play [Philadelphia opening], February 16, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Book and Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner Music by John Barry
  - Look, Ma, I'm Dancin'!, [1948] (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Book by Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee Music and Lyrics by Hugh Martin
  - Look, Ma, I'm Dancin'!, [1948] (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Look to the Lilies, [1970] (Box 11, Folder 20)
    Book by Leonard Spigelgass Music by Jule Styne Lyrics by Sammy Cahn
  - Louisiana Purchase, [1940] (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Book by Morrie Ryskind Music and Lyrics by Irving Berlin
  - Love Life, [1948] (Box 11, Folder 22)
    [Book and Lyrics by Alan Jay Lerner Music by Kurt Weill]
  - Ma'am: A New Musical, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Madame Aphrodite: A Play with Music, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Book by Tad Mosel Music and Lyrics by Terry Herman
  - Magdalena: A Musical Adventure [revised], 1986 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Book by Frederick Hazlitt Brennan and Homer Curran Music by Heitor Villa-Lobos Lyrics by Robert Wright and George Forrest
  - Maggie May: A Musical, undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
    by Lionel Hart and Alun Owen
  - Mame, March 1966 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    unrevised old script
  - Manhattan Mary, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Book by George White and Billy K. Wells Music by Ray Henderson Lyrics by BG DeSylva and Lew Brown
  - Marathon '33: A Musical Play, Spring, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    by June Havoc
  - Marilyn: An American Fable, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Book by Dolores Quinton Music and Lyrics by Jeannie Napoli, Doug Frank, Gary Portnoy, Beth Lawrence and Norman Thalheimer
  - Marilyn: The Musical, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Book and Lyrics by Jacques Wilson Music by Mort Garson
  - Married Alive, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Book by Nunnally Johnson Music by Jule Styne Lyrics by E.Y. Harburg
  - Mary: A Musical Comedy in Two Acts, [1920] (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Book by Otto Harbach and Frank Mandel Music by Louis Hirsch Lyrics by Otto Harbach
  - Mary Jane McKane, [1923] (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Book and Lyrics by Wm. Cary Duncan and Oscar Hammerstein, 2nd Music by Vincent Youmans and Herbert Stothart
  - Meet the People, [1940] (Box 12, Folder 7)
    by Henry Meyers, Edward Eliscu and Jay Gorney
  - Meet the People, [1940] (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Merrily We Roll Along, August 10, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Book by George Furth Music and lyrics by Stephen Sondheim Directed by Harold Prince
  - (Merry-Go-Round) Ship Ahoy: An Intimate Revue, [1927] (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Book and Lyrics by Morrie Ryskind and Howard Dietz Music by Henry Souvanie and Jay Gorney
  - The Merry Widow [final version], 1980 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Book and Lyrics by Victor M. Leon and Leo Stein Music by Franz Lehar
  - Merton of the Movies: A Musical, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Book by Mel Shapiro Music by Gary William Friedman Lyrics by Robert Lorick
  - Metropolis [revised], February 8, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Book and Lyrics by Dusty Hughes and Joe Brooks Music by Joe Brooks
  - Newspaper clipping, advertisement for "Metropolis", March 17, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Mexican Hayride, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Book by Herbert and Dorothy Fields Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter
  - Milk and Honey: A Musical Play, [1961] (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Book by Don Appell Music and Lyrics by Jerry Herman
  - Minnie's Boys, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Book by Arthur Marx Music by Larry Grossman Lyrics by Hal Hackady
  - Minsky's, October 23, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Book by Bob Martin Music by Charles Strouse Lyrics by Susan Birkenhead
    Third draft
  - Les Miserables, January 1986 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    Book by Alain Boublil and Claude Michel Schonberg Music by Claude Michel Schonberg Lyrics by Herbert Kretzmer
  - Les Miserables [New York production], undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Miss Liberty, 1949 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Book by Robert E. Sherwood Music and Lyrics by Irving Berlin
  - Miss Saigon [fourth draft], July 9, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Molly: A Musical Comedy, [1973] (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Book by Louis Garfinkle and Leonard Adelson Music by Jerry Livingston Lyrics by Leonard Adelson and Mack Davis
  - Molly: A Musical Comedy, [1973] (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Moonlight and Magnolias [revised rehearsal draft], February 18, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    by Ron Hutchinson
  - Mr. President, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    Book by Howard Lindsay and Russell Crouse Music and Lyrics by Irving Berlin
  - Mr. Wonderful, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    Book by Joseph Stein and Will Glickman Music and Lyrics by Jerry Bock, Larry Holofcener and George Weiss
  - Much Ado About Love, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Music Is, [1976] (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Book by George Abbott Music by Richard Adler Lyrics by Will Holt
  - Music Is, with revision pages, [1976] (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - My Fair Lady, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - My One and Only: A Musical Comedy [final production script], 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Book by Peter Stone and Timothy S. Mayer Music by George Gershwin Lyrics by Ira Gershwin
  - The Mystery of Edwin Drood: A Musical [version G, Broadway post-opening script], December 11, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    by Rupert Holmes
  - Nefertiti: A Musical Play, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Book and Lyrics Christopher Gore Music by David Spangler
  - The New Yorkers: A Sociological Musical Satire, [1930] (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Book by Herbert Fields Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter
  - Nick and Nora, November 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Book by Arthur Laurents Music by Charles Strouse Lyrics by Richard Maltby, Jr.
  - The Night Boat, 1920 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Book and Lyrics by Anne Caldwell Music by Jerome Kern
  - The Night They Raided Minsky's [revised], August 1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Book by Evan Hunter Music by Charles Strouse Lyrics by Susan Birkenhead
  - Nine [preliminary production script], [1982] (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - No, No, Nanette: The New 1925 Musical (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Book by Otto Harbach and Frank Mandel Music by Vincent Youmans Lyrics by Irving Caesar and Otto Harbach
  - Nowhere to Go but Up: The Musical Saga of Izzy and Moe [3rd mimeo], August 31, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Book and Lyrics by James Lipton Music by Sol Berkowitz
  - Nymph Errant, October 6, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Book by Romney Brent Music and Lyrics by Cole Porter